David Bromberg collection
American Folklife Center, Library of Congress
Guides to the Collections in the Archive of Folk Culture
David Bromberg collection ca. 1962-2013
AFC 2015/043
Bromberg, David, 1945-
760 items (6 linear feet)
moving images: 61 videocassettes (U-Matic): sound, color; 3/4 in.
moving images: 10 video reels: sound, color; 1 in.
moving images: 1 videocassette (VHS): sound, color.
sound recordings: 2 sound discs (acetate): analog; 12 in.
graphic images: 133 photographs: prints, black and white, color.
manuscripts: 62 folders (550 items)
Archive of Folk Culture, American Folklife Center, Library of Congress Washington, D.C.
Collection of video recordings, photographs, promotional and publicity materials, clippings, posters, and ephemera from the career of David Bromberg, musician, singer-songwriter, and luthier, from around 1962 to 2013, including recordings of his performances at concerts and folk festivals around the United States as well as overseas and various interviews with Bromberg. Includes photographs of other folk music and popular music performers.
Selected Search Terms
The following terms have been used to index the description of this collection in the LC Catalog. They are grouped by name of person or organization, by subject or location, and by occupation and listed alphabetically.
People
Bromberg, David, 1945-; Bromberg, David, 1945-; Josephson, Nancy, 1955-
Subjects
Blues (Music); Folk festivals--United States.; Folk music--United States.; Folk singers--United States--Interviews.; Popular music--United States.
Form/Genre
Clippings.; Correspondence.; Filmed interviews.; Photographs.; Posters.
Arrangement
Moving image material was arranged and described as a separate series (Series 1. Moving image items) before transfer to the Packard Campus for Audio-Visual Conservation. The rest of the materials are arranged into Series 2. Photographs, manuscripts, and sound recordings. Subseries within series 2 are arranged in groupings provided by the donor with descriptions at the item-level.
Physical numbering is not always consecutive due to the varying sizes of photographic prints and manuscripts.
Acquisition
David Bromberg and Nancy Josephson; 2015.
Access and Restrictions
Collection is open for research; access to collection materials may be restricted. To request materials, please contact the Folklife Reading Room at http://hdl.loc.gov/loc.afc/folklife.contact
Biographical Note
David Bromberg was born on September 19, 1945, in Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, and raised in Tarrytown, New York. He is a multi-instrumentalist, singer, and songwriter, and has collaborated with a a variety of musicians, including John Hartford, Willie Nelson, and Jerry Jeff Walker. Though he is known for the fingerpicking blues style he learned while studying under Reverend Gary Davis, Bromberg's music covers various American styles, such as bluegrass, country, jazz, and rock and roll. During a hiatus from his musical performance career, Bromberg became a violin expert, ultimately building an extensive collection of American-built violins and opening a violin sales and repair shop in Wilmington, Delaware, with his wife, Nancy Josephson.
Scope and Content
Collection of video recordings, photographs, promotional and publicity materials, clippings, posters, and ephemera from the career of David Bromberg, musician, singer-songwriter, and luthier, from around 1962 to 2013, including recordings of his performances at concerts and folk festivals around the United States as well as overseas and various interviews with Bromberg. Includes photographs of other folk music and popular music performers.
Container List
- Series 1. Moving image items, ca. 1979-1990
  - Chicago show 1, February 20, 1981, 1 videocassette (U-Matic; master tape): analog, sound, color; 3/4 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV001)
    Tape 1 of a group of 17 tapes.
  - Chicago show 2, February 20, 1981, 1 videocassette (U-Matic; master tape): analog, sound, color; 3/4 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV002)
    Tape 2 of a group of 17 tapes.
  - Chicago show 3, February 20, 1981, 1 videocassette (U-Matic; master tape): analog, sound, color; 3/4 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV003)
    Tape 3 of a group of 17 tapes.
  - Chicago show 4, February 20, 1981, 1 videocassette (U-Matic; master tape): analog, sound, color; 3/4 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV004)
    Tape 4 of a group of 17 tapes.
  - Chicago show 5, February 20, 1981, 1 videocassette (U-Matic; master tape): analog, sound, color; 3/4 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV005)
    Tape 5 of a group of 17 tapes.
  - Chicago show 6, February 20, 1981, 1 videocassette (U-Matic; master tape): analog, sound, color; 3/4 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV006)
    Tape 6 of a group of 17 tapes.
  - Chicago show 7, February 20, 1981, 1 videocassette (U-Matic; master tape): analog, sound, color; 3/4 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV007)
    Tape 7 of a group of 17 tapes.
  - Chicago show 8, February 20, 1981, 1 videocassette (U-Matic; master tape): analog, sound, color; 3/4 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV008)
    Tape 8 of a group of 17 tapes.
  - Chicago show 9, February 20, 1981, 1 videocassette (U-Matic; master tape): analog, sound, color; 3/4 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV009)
    Tape 9 of a group of 17 tapes.
  - Chicago show 10, February 20, 1981, 1 videocassette (U-Matic; master tape): analog, sound, color; 3/4 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV010)
    Tape 10 of a group of 17 tapes.
  - Chicago show 11, February 20, 1981, 1 videocassette (U-Matic; master tape): analog, sound, color; 3/4 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV011)
    Tape 11 of a group of 17 tapes.
  - Chicago show 12, February 20, 1981, 1 videocassette (U-Matic; master tape): analog, sound, color; 3/4 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV012)
    Tape 12 of a group of 17 tapes.
  - Chicago show 13, February 21, 1981, 1 videocassette (U-Matic; master tape): analog, sound, color; 3/4 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV013)
    Tape 13 of a group of 17 tapes.
  - Chicago show 14, February 22, 1981, 1 videocassette (U-Matic; master tape): analog, sound, color; 3/4 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV014)
    Tape 15 of a group of 17 tapes.
  - Chicago show 16, February 22, 1981, 1 videocassette (U-Matic; master tape): analog, sound, color; 3/4 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV016)
    Tape 16 of a group of 17 tapes.
  - Chicago show 17, February 22, 1981, 1 videocassette (U-Matic; master tape): analog, sound, color; 3/4 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV017)
    Tape 17 of a group of 17 tapes.
  - Bromberg music, undated, 1 videocassette (U-Matic; master tape): analog, sound, color; 3/4 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV018)
    Tape 1 of a group of 7 tapes. Part 1: "Danger Man" intro, "Hit the Road Jack," "If You Don't Want Me, Baby," "Rock and Roll Millionaire."
  - Bromberg music, part 2, undated, 1 videocassette (U-Matic; master tape): analog, sound, color; 3/4 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV019)
    Tape 2 of a group of 7 tapes. Tracks: "Kaatskill Serenade," "Travelling Man," "Yankee's Revenge."
  - Nancy Bromberg Sot's master, undated, 1 videocassette (U-Matic; master tape): analog, sound, color; 3/4 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV020)
    Tape 3 of a group of 7 tapes.
  - Today Show off monitor, undated, 1 videocassette (U-Matic; master tape): analog, sound, color; 3/4 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV021)
    Tape 4 of a group of 7 tapes.
  - L.A., part 1, April 22, 1981, 1 videocassette (U-Matic; master tape): analog, sound, color; 3/4 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV022)
    Tape 5 of a group of 7 tapes.
  - L.A., part 2, April 22, 1981, 1 videocassette (U-Matic; master tape): analog, sound, color; 3/4 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV023)
    Tape 6 of a group of 7 tapes.
  - L.A. part 3, Ron Rainey, undated, 1 videocassette (U-Matic; master tape): analog, sound, color; 3/4 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV024)
    Tape 7 of a group of 7 tapes.
  - Band on bus, ca. 1979-1982, 1 videocassette (U-Matic; master tape): analog, sound, color; 3/4 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV025)
    Tape 1 of a group of 29 tapes.
  - BBI sound check, undated, 1 videocassette (U-Matic; master tape): analog, sound, color; 3/4 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV026)
    Tape 2 of a group of 29 tapes.
  - Back room jam, undated, 1 videocassette (U-Matic; master tape): analog, sound, color; 3/4 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV027)
    Tape 3 of a group of 29 tapes.
  - Interview with David Bromberg, undated, 1 videocassette (U-Matic; master tape): analog, sound, color; 3/4 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV028)
    Tape 4 of a group of 29 tapes.
  - David Bromberg, dressing room, undated, 1 videocassette (U-Matic; master tape): analog, sound, color; 3/4 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV029)
    Tape 5 of a group of 29 tapes.
  - Club manager interview, undated, 1 videocassette (U-Matic; master tape): analog, sound, color; 3/4 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV030)
    Tape 6 of a group of 29 tapes.
  - "Hampton Boys," day 1, undated, 1 videocassette (U-Matic; master tape): analog, sound, color; 3/4 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV031)
    Tape 7 of a group of 29 tapes.
  - Backstage, My Father's Place (Roslyn, New York music venue), undated, 1 videocassette (U-Matic; master tape): analog, sound, color; 3/4 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV032)
    Tape 8 of a group of 29 tapes.
  - Backstage, My Father's Place (Roslyn, New York music venue), undated, 1 videocassette (U-Matic; master tape): analog, sound, color; 3/4 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV033)
    Tape 9 of a group of 29 tapes.
  - Interview band/on stage, My Father's Place, undated, 1 videocassette (U-Matic; master tape): analog, sound, color; 3/4 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV034)
    Tape 10 of a group of 29 tapes.
  - Pennsylvania countryside, etc., undated, 1 videocassette (U-Matic; master tape): analog, sound, color; 3/4 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV035)
    Tape 11 of a group of 29 tapes.
  - My Father's Place/kitchen/club owner interview, David Bromberg and Richie Giordano outside hotel, undated, 1 videocassette (U-Matic; master tape): analog, sound, color; 3/4 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV036)
    Tape 12 of a group of 29 tapes.
  - David Bromberg interview, on stage, Temple University, Philadelphia, Pennsylvania, undated, 1 videocassette (U-Matic; master tape): analog, sound, color; 3/4 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV037)
    Tape 13 of a group of 29 tapes.
  - Temple University backstage, undated, 1 videocassette (U-Matic; master tape): analog, sound, color; 3/4 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV038)
    Tape 14 of a group of 29 tapes.
  - On stage, Temple University, undated, 1 videocassette (U-Matic; master tape): analog, sound, color; 3/4 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV039)
    Tape 15 of a group of 29 tapes.
  - On stage, Temple University, undated, 1 videocassette (U-Matic; master tape): analog, sound, color; 3/4 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV040)
    Tape 16 of a group of 29 tapes.
  - WNEW interview, undated, 1 videocassette (U-Matic; master tape): analog, sound, color; 3/4 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV041)
    Tape 17 of a group of 29 tapes.
  - Dave Herman WNEW interview, undated, 1 videocassette (U-Matic; master tape): analog, sound, color; 3/4 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV042)
    Tape 18 of a group of 29 tapes.
  - Zu - Asbury Park, undated, 1 videocassette (U-Matic; master tape): analog, sound, color; 3/4 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV043)
    Tape 19 of a group of 29 tapes.
  - Asbury Park backstage, undated, 1 videocassette (U-Matic; master tape): analog, sound, color; 3/4 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV044)
    Tape 20 of a group of 29 tapes.
  - Paramount Theater, on stage and backstage, undated, 1 videocassette (U-Matic; master tape): analog, sound, color; 3/4 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV045)
    Tape 21 of a group of 29 tapes.
  - Paramount Theater, on stage, undated, 1 videocassette (U-Matic; master tape): analog, sound, color; 3/4 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV046)
    Tape 22 of a group of 29 tapes.
  - Paramount Theater, on stage and backstage, undated, 1 videocassette (U-Matic; master tape): analog, sound, color; 3/4 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV047)
    Tape 23 of a group of 29 tapes.
  - Mr. and Mrs. Bromberg interview, undated, 1 videocassette (U-Matic; master tape): analog, sound, color; 3/4 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV048)
    Tape 24 of a group of 29 tapes.
  - Bromberg house and family, undated, 1 videocassette (U-Matic; master tape): analog, sound, color; 3/4 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV049)
    Tape 25 of a group of 29 tapes.
  - Central Park soundcheck, undated, 1 videocassette (U-Matic; master tape): analog, sound, color; 3/4 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV050)
    Tape 26 of a group of 29 tapes.
  - Wollman Stage, Central Park concert, undated, 1 videocassette (U-Matic; master tape): analog, sound, color; 3/4 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV051)
    Tape 27 of a group of 29 tapes.
  - Wollman Stage, Bromberg family, street scene Bottom Line, undated, 1 videocassette (U-Matic; master tape): analog, sound, color; 3/4 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV052)
    Tape 28 of a group of 29 tapes.
  - Bottom Line and Crowls backstage, undated, 1 videocassette (U-Matic; master tape): analog, sound, color; 3/4 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV053)
    Tape 29 of a group of 29 tapes.
  - David Bromberg Special PGM, reel 1, August 11, 1980, 1 sound videocassette (U-matic): analog. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV054)
    Tape 1 of a group of 8 tapes.
  - David Bromberg Special PGM, reel 2, August 11, 1980, 1 sound videocassette (U-matic): analog. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV055)
    Tape 2 of a group of 8 tapes.
  - Assemble stock, Chicago, Central Park, undated, 1 sound videocassette (U-matic): analog. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV056)
    Tape 3 of a group of 8 tapes.
  - David Bromberg PGM, reel 1, August 11, 1980, 1 sound videocassette (U-matic): analog. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV057)
    Tape 4 of a group of 8 tapes.
  - David Bromberg PGM, reel 1, part 2, August 11, 1980, 1 sound videocassette (U-matic): analog. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV058)
    Tape 5 of a group of 8 tapes.
  - David Bromberg PGM, July 1, 1981, 1 sound videocassette (U-matic): analog. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV059)
    Tape 6 of a group of 8 tapes. Tracks: "If You Don't Want Me," Danger Man," "Hit the Road Jack."
  - Today Show air check, March 17, 1981, 1 sound videocassette (U-matic): analog. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV060)
    Tape 7 of a group of 8 tapes.
  - Assemble stock, undated, 1 sound videocassette (U-matic): analog. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV061)
    Tape 8 of a group of 8 tapes. Tracks: "Danger Man," "Kaatskill."
  - Concert footage, multi camera video takes, August 11, 1980, 1 video reel (master broadcast video): sound, color; 1 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV062)
    Bromberg 51, reel 1. Bromberg concert. Audio: ch. 1 (PCM), ch. 2 (EFX), ch. 3 (TC).
  - Concert footage, multi camera video takes, August 11, 1980, 1 video reel (master broadcast video): sound, color; 1 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV063)
    Bromberg 41. Cam 4 ISO / TRT 63 [or 65] / reel 1.
  - Concert footage, multi camera video takes, August 11, 1980, 1 video reel (master broadcast video; 55 min.): sound, color; 1 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV064)
    Bromberg. Cam 3 ISO / reel 1 / TRT 55 min.
  - Concert footage, multi camera video takes, August 11, 1980, 1 video reel (master broadcast video): sound, color; 1 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV065)
    Bromberg 43 / Cam 4 ISO / VTR 1 / reel 3.
  - Concert footage, multi camera video takes, August 11, 1980, 1 video reel (master broadcast video): sound, color; 1 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV066)
    Bromberg 53 / VTR 1 / reel 3. Audio: ch. 1 (PCM), ch. 2 (EFX), ch. 3 (TC).
  - Concert footage, multi camera video takes, August 11, 1980, 1 video reel (master broadcast video; 55 min.): sound, color; 1 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV067)
    Bromberg 42 / Cam 4 ISO / reel 2 / TRT 55 min.
  - Bromberg concert, undated, 1 video reel (master broadcast video): sound, color; 1 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV068)
    Bromberg 32.
  - Bromberg concert, undated, 1 video reel (master broadcast video): sound, color; 1 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV069)
    Bromberg 33.
  - Bromberg concert, undated, 1 video reel (master broadcast video): sound, color; 1 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV070)
    Bromberg 25 / VTR 1 / reel 2. Container spine and label on tape reel say "Bromberg 52."
  - Bromberg concert, undated, 1 video reel (master broadcast video; 50 min.): sound, color; 1 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV071)
    David Bromberg 23 / Cam 2 ISO / reel 3 TRT 50
  - Barnacle Bills, St. Thomas. David Bromberg with Chicago MVPs. Dave Mason sitting in., January 5, 1990, 1 sound videocassette (VHS): analog. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: MV072)
- Series 2. Photographs, manuscripts, and sound recordings, ca. 1962-2013
  - Subseries 1. Group 1, ca. 1965-2012
    - Contact sheet, photos by David Bromberg (1-4), ca. 1970-1971, 4 photographic prints (Box 2)
      Nashville, Tennessee, during breaks from recording "Aereoplane." Photos featuring John Hartford (with girlfriend Nwanda), Norman Blake, Tut Taylor, Vassar Clements, and Randy Wood (fixing banjo, most likely at the shop "GTR" (George, Tut, Randy).
    - Nancy Josephson on bass, David Bromberg, Johnny Duke (Lippincott), guitar, 1 photographic print (Box 1)
    - David Bromberg, Los Angeles, California, undated, 1 photographic print (Box 1)
      Grammy nomination photograph. For album "Try Me One More Time."
    - Jerry Jeff Walker and David Bromberg at Northwestern University, Evanston, Illinois, ca. 1973-1978, 1 photographic print (Box 1)
      Photograph by Charles Seton.
    - Big band photograph, October 16, 1997, 1 photographic print (Box 1)
      Left-Right: John Firmin, Peter Ecklund, Curt Lindbergh, David [surname unknown] on drums, Robert Armiot [surname spelling unknown], Mimi Hart, Nancy Josephson, Jeff Wisor, Dick Fegy.
    - John Scholle and David Bromberg, ca. 1965-1970, 1 photographic print (Box 1)
      David Bromberg's apartment.
    - "Mississippi Blind Driveways," ca. 1966, 1 photographic print (Box 1)
      David Bromberg, Paul Siebel, Jody Stecher. Photograph by Steve Somerstein.
    - David Bromberg with Mary Travers, Peter Yarrow, and Freebo, undated, 1 photographic print (Box 1)
    - Waylon Jennings and David Bromberg, undated, 1 photographic print (Box 1)
      Sam Emerson photograph.
    - David Bromberg with Phoebe Snow, undated, 1 photographic print (Box 1)
    - David Bromberg with Phoebe Snow, undated, 1 photographic print (Box 1)
    - Jim Ringer, Jay Ungar, David Bromberg, undated, 1 photographic print (Box 1)
    - Michael Doucet and David Bromberg, undated, 1 photographic print (Box 1)
    - David Bromberg and Al Kooper, undated, 1 photographic print (Box 1)
      Sam Emerson photograph
    - Bonnie Raitt, David Bromberg, Rona Barett [surname spelling unknown], undated, 1 photographic print (Box 1)
      Philadelphia Folk Festival.
    - David Bromberg and Rosalie Sorrels, undated, 1 photographic print (Box 2)
      Jim McGuire photograph.
    - Peter Wernick, David Bromberg, and Joan Leonard, undated, 1 photographic print (Box 1)
    - David Bromberg and Jorma Kaukonen, undated, 1 photographic print (Box 1)
      Mike Thut photograph. Bolton Center, Long Island, New York.
    - David Bromberg and Jorma Kaukonen, undated, 1 photographic print (Box 1)
    - David Bromberg, Jorma Kaukonen, and Barry Mitterhoff, undated, 1 photographic print (Box 1)
    - Jack Cassidy, Jorma Kaukonen, Barry Mitterhoff, and David Bromberg, undated, 1 photographic print (Box 1)
    - Bob Dylan, Leon Redbone, David Bromberg, undated, 1 photographic print (Box 1)
    - Behind World Control Studios in Philadelphia during recording of first album, "David Bromberg," 1972, 1 photographic print (Box 1)
      Standing (Left-Right): David Nichtern, Steve Mosely, Donnie Sarlin, Will Scarlet. Seated (Left-Right): Winnie Winston, Jody Stecher, David Bromberg, Steve Burgh.
    - Michael Cooney and David, Mariposa Folk Festival, 1971, 1 photographic print (Box 1)
    - David Bromberg, Jesse Ed David with wife and child, undated, 1 photographic print (Box 1)
    - Winnie Winston, Jody Stecher, and David Bromberg, undated, 1 photographic print (Box 1)
      WBAI radio, Bob Foss' show.
    - Jeff Wisor, John Firmin, David Bromberg, John McQueen, Nancy Josephson, Gene Johnson, Dick Fegy, undated, 1 photographic print (Box 1)
      Sarah Shoaf photograph.
    - Jim Ringer, Mary McCaslin, Jay Ungar, Deb [surname unknown], David Bromberg, undated, 1 photographic print (Box 1)
      The Ark, Ann Arbor, Michigan.
    - Happy Traum and David Bromberg, ca. 1990-1999, 1 photographic print (Box 1)
      Backstage at Tarrytown Music Hall, Tarrytown, New York. Photograph by Thom Wolke.
    - Michael Cooney, David Bromberg, Aly Bain, Mike Whelan, undated, 1 photographic print (Box 1)
      Iowa. Pre "Boys of the Lough."
    - David Bromberg, (steel guitar player), Leland Sklar, and Lyle Lovett, 2012, 1 photographic print (Box 1)
      The Grand Opera, Wilmington, Delaware
    - Doug Kershaw and David Bromberg, 1971, 1 photographic print (Box 1)
    - John Hartford, Eric Frandsen, David Bromberg, and Tom Paxton, ca. 1970-1972, 1 photographic print (Box 3)
      Jim McGuire photograph. Philadelphia Folk Festival.
    - David Bromberg and Janis Ian, undated, 1 photographic print (Box 1)
  - Subseries 2. Group 2, 1967-1968, 1 photographic print
    - Ned Wright, William Jones, Richard Sparles, Lance Wakely, and David Bromberg, ca. 1967, 8 photographic prints (Box 1)
      Black and white 8x10 photographic prints. Southeast Asia United States Information Service, Manila and Kuala Lampur.
    - The Phoenix Singers in San Jose, Costa Rica, ca. 1968, 1 photographic print (Box 1)
      South America tour lineup: Ned Wright, William Jones, Richard Sparks, Mark Horowitz, and David Bromberg.
    - Postcard with photograph of the band at the Caracas, Venezuela airport, 1968, 1 photographic print (Box 1)
      10. Postcard with photograph by David Bromberg to then girlfriend, Trudy Wrigley.
    - Photograph of Ned Wright by David Bromberg, ca. 1968, 1 photographic print (Box 1)
    - Airport stop photograph by David Bromberg, ca. 1968, 1 photographic print (Box 1)
    - The Phoenix Singers program, 1968, 1 paper program (Box 1)
    - David Bromberg United States Information Service photograph, Manila, ca. 1967-1968, 1 photographic print (Box 1)
  - Subseries 3. Group 3, ca. 1972-2003
    - David Bromberg and Norman Blake, May 12, 1974, Photographic print on foam (Box 3)
      Photograph by Dennis Deloria.
    - David Bromberg and Norman Blake promo photograph, ca. 1972-1974, Photographic print on foam (Box 3)
      Photograph by Jim McGuire.
    - David Bromberg and Norman Blake promo photograph, ca. 1972-1974, Photographic print on foam (Box 3)
    - Original sheet music for Nobody's [Fault But Mine], 1975, manuscript (sheet music) (Box 3)
      Violin parts probably by Evan Stover.
    - Laminated advertisement from Columbia Records for album, "David Bromberg," ca. 1972, manuscript (Box 2)
    - Newspaper clipping for Columbia Records advertisement for album, "Midnight on the Water," ca. 1975, manuscript (Box 3)
    - Original acetate for "Demon in Disguise," demo, ca. 1972, 1 sound disc: 12 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: SR001)
    - Original acetate for "Demon in Disguise," demo, ca. 1972, 1 sound disc: 12 in. (Item-id AFC 2015/043: SR002)
    - 45 rpm record for songs "Such a Night" and "Bluebird," 1976, 45 rpm record (Item-id AFC 2015/043: SR003)
      Fantasy Records.
    - Village of Tarrytown proclamation for "David Bromberg Day," October 26, 2003, manuscript (Box-folder 4)
    - "Honorary Citizen" certificate for David Bromberg from the mayor of New Orleans, Louisiana, November 17, 1984, manuscript (Box-folder 4)
  - Subseries 4. Group 4, ca. 1967-2011
    - Philadelphia Inquirer, August 14, 2011, manuscript (Box-folder 5/1)
      Section H, page 1. "One of the Folk" article.